Uh, this is module 8.6,
and in this one we're gonna talk about exporting different scroll stopper
variations. Now I want to preface this with this particular project,
um,
we actually scripted and shot multiple different scroll stoppers.
And so we already had those already lined up. Um, and in,
in certain cases you don't necessarily have those,
or maybe you need to create some for yourself. Um,
in other cases you need to search through your footage and find, uh,
scroll stoppers and hooks,
and I'll create a separate tutorial on how I like to do that to extract the
best, uh, you know, one-liners or reactions,
whatever they may be from your UGCs, to create your own inventory of,
of good hooks. So in this example, I like that it's very clear and simple,
you know, you know what they are. We, we shot a bunch of 'em.
So you can see exactly the graphic aspect of a, of a, of a strong hook.
As you can tell over here, we've got these,
these are all intentional to be hooks. So, uh,
whether you're an editor or you, you know,
you work on everything in your business,
I highly recommend shooting intentional hooks so that you have more
ammunition to test, uh, out in the field.
So the first step to getting your hooks lined up is to
make sure that you give yourself a little bit of extra space here on the
first couple seconds. The reason is, uh,
different hooks or different shots have different lengths and it's gonna
be a lot harder to drag something in here. If it's longer,
it's gonna push your footage back. It's gonna, yeah, it's just kind of annoying.
So what I like to do is hit a and just move everything down like
a few seconds. There's no exact placement for it.
And now you've got a little bit more of a gap here.
So I'm just gonna move in a little closer here. I'm gonna, I'm gonna fix my, uh,
fix my voiceover here. Just, I lost 60 pounds with weightless. Weightless, okay,
perfect. So this is gonna be included in the, in the hook.
And one thing I want to mention as well, when you're testing hooks,
you want to test one variable at a time, alright? So whether that's a headline,
whether that's an audio hook, or whether that's a visual hook,
and I know we talked about the three different hooks in the previous tutorials,
but when it comes to editing,
these are the three components that you're gonna be, uh,
I would say you're gonna, you have a lever and control over.
And in this scenario, I'm gonna keep the same headline.
I'm gonna keep the same audio, but I'm gonna change the visual.
So how we're gonna do that is first and foremost,
we don't want to touch or affect any of the rest of the video right here. This,
this entire section is off limits for us. We don't wanna mess with that, okay?
And this is another thing to consider.
This is already after the fact when the client has already approved your video
and said they gave you the green light and says, okay,
we're ready for the additional variations, right?
So what I'll do is I'll just take all my clips here and actually don't need this
adjustment layer anymore,
and I'm just gonna move them all the way up past all of my
titles, just all the way up.
So I have all this extra space to just focus on my hooks.
All right?
So this is where I want to just be focusing next,
and here's what we're gonna do. So
what I'll typically do is I'll export this first version, all right?
And I'll start here and do end point, and then
go here to the very end and click O for out and make sure you trim this
extra gap right here. This is a very sneaky one,
and you wanna trim that all the way.
And from here I'm going to export this and send this to media encoder.
All right, so I'm gonna do Command M
and I'm going to send this to Media Encoder.
As you can tell, it's already opened up here.
And I just wanna double check the output file right here and make sure it's in
the right folder. So I know it's in my S ss D right now.
And we're gonna do ads x trainings, wait list, export.
And I'm gonna call this, um,
top of funnel underscore V one.
I will go over a separate tutorial about how we do naming conventions,
but for the sake of this example, I'm just gonna call it top funnel V one.
Save that there, and now I'm gonna come back to it.
I'm just gonna leave that there because what median coders gonna allow me to do
is export all of my hooks at once and have them all batch
export, so I don't have to continuously keep exporting them one at a time.
Alright?
So the next version I'm gonna do is actually what I'm gonna do because I like
this adjustment layer. I'm gonna move that and I'm gonna move this shot down.
All right. And now I'm going to show off this clip.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless weightless, awesome.
So I'm gonna bring that adjustment layer back in here.
And what I'm gonna do actually is just, I'm gonna create some space, um,
some additional tracks up here, okay?
'cause I know I have a ton of different hooks, hook potentials,
and I'm just gonna make space for 'em.
That way I can just drag and drop 'em in. All right,
let's see what this looks like. I lost 60 pounds with weightless. Weightless.
All right, so obviously we want to cut this, we want trim this here.
And I lost 60 pounds with weightless, weightless,
so, you know, I could, I could go the extra mile,
I could do a little bit more with this, but I don't think it's necessary. Like,
I can add an arrow, I could move the captions, but in this case,
I'm just gonna keep, be the same.
One thing I will say when it comes down to actual real testing is I wouldn't,
I wouldn't include this headline per se as the
hook and the visual. It's really important to have a, a,
a visual that matches the headline. So it says,
I lost 60 pounds with weightless, but maybe a better, uh, exam,
a better headline would be I finally stopped eating all my all, you know, I,
I stopped eating junk food.
That would be a better example to use or a better headline to use when
you're showing food because I lost, I lost weight.
And then you're showing a lot of food.
There could be a lot of negative feedback with that, you don't know. But, um,
or, or I, I, I don't have any more late night cravings, you know, that, that,
that's a potential too. I lost 60 pounds with weightless weightless.
So what I'm gonna do next is I'm gonna hit Command M and I'm going
to actually click on this location just so I can, um,
make sure it's in the right location and it's something I recent
and I'm gonna change that to Tofu v2, alright.
That way it just changes it ahead of time and I can go into Send Media Encoder
and now I've got my second variation there. Fantastic. Cool.
So let's do another version. Okay,
so here's another potential hook. I like this little spot right there.
And maybe for this one, you know, we can do a light little scale in.
I lost 60 pounds with Weightless. Yeah, that looks pretty cool.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless. Weightless is fantastic.
Now I'm just gonna export this hook. Same thing over here.
Changed the name Top Funnel V three
and Good Send to Media Encoder.
And for the sake of this example, let's just do,
let's do one more example. Yeah, this one's good. This
Actually, I think I'm going to try to rotate this shot.
I think that's what we initially intended for this. Oh, no,
that's not gonna work.
I
Might, I lost 60 pounds with weightless.
I'll leave it. Okay,
I'm gonna take off the adjustment later just for this shot. Why not?
I lost 60 pounds with weightless. So what I did there was I,
I took that long shot and then I, uh,
I sped it up all the way so it fit in that section. Weightless,
I lost 60 pounds with weightless, weightless. Cool.
So from there, I'm gonna export that variation again,
change this to tofu. I think we're on V four now,
sent to Median Coder and great. So,
uh, for that example, I'm just gonna roll with those four hooks,
but I could keep going, right?
I can keep exporting different variations and I'm just gonna click play right
here and let that do its thing. So I'll be right back.
Alright, there we go. That was just a few minutes later. Super fast.
So let's just review these really quickly.
And now we've got four different variations of the same ad.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless.
Weightless is helping transform the health of thousands of Americans includes
three blah blah, blah, ingredients over, blah, blah, blah.
People are losing 17.8 pounds. You've gotta check this out.
It's not available at any pharmacy. Go to wait list today.
That's really funny 'cause I w I forgot that I did the voiceover and
it's like blah, blah, blah. All right. I lost 60 pounds with weightless.
Weightless is helping. I lost 60 pounds with weightless. Weightless.
I lost 60 pounds with weightless. Weightless is helping transform. All right,
awesome. I honestly think obviously without my voiceover the better one,
it's helping. Well these videos could definitely perform well and um,
that's pretty much the whole process. So, uh, I'll go in another tutorial,
breaking down how I organize these into an Airtable and track
the performance of things. But from start to finish,
that is the entire process of creating a video ad in
this particular style, uh, with these particular shots.
Now there's a lot of different, uh, other possibilities here in terms of,
of editing styles, but we will go over that in a different tutorial.
I hope you found this one helpful and if you have any questions,
obviously reach out to us and we'll be happy to answer any of them.
And if we're missing anything, please let us know.
But I look forward to seeing you guys in the next tutorial.
We're gonna be covering some more awesome stuff. Alright,
thank you so much for watching.